startupguys.net 2019-11-08

# Privacy Policy » StartupGuys.net

At StartupGuys.net we are strongly committed to protect your privacy in order to provide you safe online experience. This Privacy Policy discusses the types of information we collect from our users. If you’re not comfortable with our Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with information discussed below or otherwise use the Site.

**1- Information We Collect through Cookies**

When you visit StartupGuys.net, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device to identify your browser. Cookies are small files containing a string of characters that uniquely identify your browser. We use cookies to track user trends so we can provide you the best services time to time.

Most browsers are set up to accept cookies by default, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Doing so may not let StartupGuys.net work properly for you.

Our cookies do not collect personal information that you provide to us during the registration process, but they do collect other information such as the following:

• Internet service provider from which you access the Internet.

• Internet address of the site from which you clicked our link.

• The date and time you access the Site and pages you visit.

• Your computer’s IP address, operating system information & browser type and version etc.

• Demographic information.

• Personal Information

We collect your personal information like your name, email address, phone number, gender and location at the time of registration. Registered users at StartupGuys.net have more privileges than that of normal visitors. If you’re not comfortable in providing this information, you must not proceed with registration on site.

**2- Collection of Information by Third Parties**

StartupGuys.net may include third-party advertising and links to other websites who collect your personal information on their websites. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, and other technologies to collect stats about their campaigns and store your information. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other technologies that our advertisers may use. Check their respective privacy policies for further assistance.

**3- Information Sharing**  
We do not share any of the above information with any third party, except trusted partners. We are constantly developing our business and we might sell or buy businesses or their assets, or engage in transfers, acquisitions, mergers, restructurings, changes of control or similar transactions. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets, and your information will be subjected to such a transfer.

**4- Disclosure**  
This Privacy Policy applies to StartupGuys.net services only. We do not take responsibility and have no control over the content/services of the sites being advertized with us. These sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer or other device to collect data and personal information from you.

**5- Changes to the Privacy Policy**

At StartupGuys.net we strive to provide our users with the best services. In order to improve our services this Privacy Policy may change from time to time and so the page will be updated. If you have any queries or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time via StartupGuys.net(at)gmail.com.
